<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Hype Driven Dev</title>
    <link>https://hypedrivendev.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Hype Driven Dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 10:52:42 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hypedrivendev.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Working around the world</title>
      <link>https://hypedrivendev.io/post/2019/working-around-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 10:52:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hypedrivendev.io/post/2019/working-around-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Hey, I&amp;#8217;m back! I have been traveling with my girlfriend for a few months around North and South America, and the South Pole. It has been great, as you can imagine. As a first blog post after this long break, I wanted to share with you a few thoughts about traveling, and working around the world, as I did for more than a year over 2 trips and 6 continents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going nomad for a few months</title>
      <link>https://hypedrivendev.io/post/2017/going-nomad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 14:26:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hypedrivendev.io/post/2017/going-nomad/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, I packed all my things in a box and rented my apartment in France. Since then, I&amp;#8217;ve been traveling with my girlfriend, all our lives packed in two backpacks :).
 We plan to travel for 6 months, and to visit a few countries that we don&amp;#8217;t know yet. This is not the first time that we do this, but it&amp;#8217;s still exciting and fun and scary!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to blogging</title>
      <link>https://hypedrivendev.io/post/2017/back-to-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 14:26:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hypedrivendev.io/post/2017/back-to-blogging/</guid>
      <description>Hey, hello there!
 It&amp;#8217;s been a while since I wrote something on my personal blog (as you may know I was busy writing an ebook about Angular).
 My old blog was using Wordpress, and I was not really into going back there :). The blog of Ninja Squad is using Jekyll, and even if it works great, I&amp;#8217;m a bit tired of it.
 So the first task was to look for a new static blog generator.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>